planet-tek.com 2011-09-11

# Planet-Tek Systems - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Planet-Tek Systems™ is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Planet-Tek Systems™ reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time without prior notice. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it. This policy is effective from 01.01.2008

### Information We Collect

Planet-Tek Systems™ gathers two types of information about users:

  * Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters.
  * Information Planet-Tek Systems™ gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and to help us better understand the demographics of our audience. Under no circumstances does Planet-Tek Systems™ divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.

### Data Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at +1.416.860.1100 or send us an email at [info@planet-tek.com](mailto:%20info@planet-tek.com).

back to planet-tek.com
